Nirjal Paudel



nirjalpaudel54312@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/nirjalpaudel



+9779863948081



https://nirjalpaudel.com.np

Summary

Software engineer with 4+ years of experience in application development. I have a strong communication, leadership and technical background developing API and migrating to new platforms like AWS. Keeping the business needs in priority, I have led many applications to success.

I love to document my various learning thorugh blogs.

Experience

Senior Software Engineer

Cleanilo

Mar 2021 - Sep 2022 (1 year 7 months)

Cleanilo is a leading professional cleaning company offering a wide range of services to keep your home sparkling. It brings both end of the cleaning pipeline togther. Over here, my responsibilities build thier website from ground up. My achievement over there includes:

- Built the integration of payments across the pipeline
- Spearheaded the project development

Senior Software Engineer

Hyteno

Nov 2020 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Hyteno provides affordable digital solutions for restaurants to help them grow, and build customer loyalty. It provides many features like unified social media, marketing and website support. My key achievements included:

- Built the entire hyteno backend
- Drive the migration of older hyteno to AWS
- Led the project development
- Scaled project to handle multi country

Software Engineer

Takeo

Feb 2023 - Apr 2023 (3 months)

TakeoAI is a company in New York, USA that provides bootcamp which guides you to enter to the wild west of software development. The service of takeo crosses international border and is one of the top education provders of bootcamp in the USA and Canada. My responsibilites in Takeo.Al was to build new feature for their registaration and take part in key descisions regarding AWS services.



Software Engineer

Lanceme Up

Jun 2021 - Jan 2022 (8 months)

Lanceme Up is an IT service company at Lalitpur, Nepal. Lanceme Up provides various IT and non IT services to business all around the world. My primary job at Lanceme Up was to help them architect

their backend and system design. I led their migration into AWS, helped them reduced cost of their infrasturcture and mentored junior developers on building new features.

Back End Developer

Softshala Nepal

Apr 2021 - Jan 2022 (10 months)

Softshala Nepal is a digital consulting company and software development firm that builds software solutions for their clients and has in house products as well. In Softshala my responsibilities were to build their video streaming service from scratch and make their share marketing app as fast as possible. Some of the achievements over there were:

- Conceptualized the best way to build their new solution
- Build one of the most performant share market application in Nepal

Education



Madan Bhandari Memorial College

Bsc Csit, Computer Science

2019 - 2023

Studying CS degress has been one of the blessing. It supplies me with a new angle to see all the work I have built. It helped me weigh tradeoff between the various choices that arises during my development.

Little Angel College

10 +2, Physical Sciences

2018 - 2019

Learning physical science and its impact on the world we are living in was felt inspiring to me. I am glad that I learned a lot durijg my days in Little Angel's College

Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS) • GraphQL • JavaScript • SQL • Node.js • Web Development • Version Control • NoSQL • MongoDB • Django

Honors & Awards

IR Renegade Hackathon - Renegade Insurance

Dec 2022



Ku hackfest 2021 winner - Major League Hacking

Mar 2021

Provathan Hackathan - CSIT Association of Nepal

Sep 2021